[
  {
    "question": "1: What is your previous dog experience?",
    "id": 0,
    "answers": ["have never owned a dog", "owned a dog in the past", "currently have have a dog(s)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "2: Which best describes your current living situation?",
    "id": 1,
    "answers": ["apartment", "house with small yard", "house with large yard"]
  },
  {
    "question": "3: Do any children live in your home? If yes, approximately how old are they?",
    "id": 2,
    "answers": ["no", "0-10 years old", "10+ years old"]
  },
  {
    "question": "4: What amount of shedding will you tolerate?",
    "id": 3,
    "answers": ["minimal to none", "moderate shedding", "heavy or seasonal shedding"]
  },
  {
    "question": "5: What amount of barking will you tolerate?",
    "id": 4,
    "answers": ["minimal", "here and there", "frequent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "6: How active are you?",
    "id": 5,
    "answers": ["couch potato", "excercise here and there", "daily excercise"]
  },
  {
    "question": "7: Are you willing to house train your new dog?",
    "id": 6,
    "answers": ["yes", "no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "8: Do you want a dog that will fit in a carry-on?",
    "id": 7,
    "answers": ["yes", "no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "9: How much time can you commit to training your new dog?",
    "id": 8,
    "answers": ["1-4 hours per week", "4-9 hours per week", "10 or more hours per week"]
  },
  {
    "question": "10: Are you willing to pay to have your dog groomed?",
    "id": 9,
    "answers": ["yes", "no"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you for completing the survey!",
    "id": 10,
    "answers": [""]
  }
]